翻译、时间轴、压制：up主
Gaijin Entertainment presents
Gaijin Entertainment出品
the Shooting Range
You are watching The Shooting Range,
你正在观看the Shooting Range
a weekly show for all tankers and airmen of War Thunder.
这是一档给战争雷霆玩家提供的周播节目
In this episode…
在这一集
Plywood Wonder and the Squadron of Furies;
赛艇传奇和中队愤怒
The Greatest Raid of All: how the Brits stormed St Nazaire;
最强的突袭 英国人如何猛攻圣纳泽尔
Hotline: the developers answer questions that you've left in the comments!
热线 开发者将回答评论区中的问题
But first, let's start with everything we can tell about Naval Warfare.
但首先 我们来聊聊海战的消息
TM
We've kept you in the dark for a long time.
Soon  的时间内 我们对此无可奉告
You've kept bombarding us with questions nevertheless.
尽管你们跑得比香港记者还快
And finally we can give you some answers.
最后我们可以明确地告诉你
First and foremost: the closed beta is almost here.
首先 内测即将开始
It will start later this year.
它将于今年晚些时候启动
There are two ways to get in: you can be invited,
有两种方式可获得内测资格 你可以被邀（钦）请（定）
or you can purchase one of the two naval Starter packs with unique ships,
或者你可以购买海军入门包中的任意一个 它们都有着不同的船只
which are available in our store right now.
这可以从我们商店中获得
The open beta phase will start next year.
公测将于明年启动
The same question was popping up over and over again:
同样的问题总是被翻出来问
what nations will get ships?
什么国家会有船
The answer is simple: all of them.
答案很简单 每个国家
Every side of the conflict will get its own fleet.
作战的双方都会有自己的船队
What's important, it's that we decided to focus on the fast attack-based craft,
更重要的是 我们决定把重点放在快速攻击赛艇
such as torpedo boats, which are rarely reproduced in games.
譬如鱼雷艇 游戏中很少有涉及到
Our internal testing showed that battles with large battleships would be too long and boring
我们的内部测试表明大型战舰的战斗实在耗时太长太无聊
or required design changes that made ships entirely unrealistic
亦或是需要对船只进行一些完全不真实的更改
and that's not the outcome that we are interested in.
这并不是我们感兴趣的结果
At the same time, you are still likely to see some bigger ships.
与此同时 你仍可能看到一些更大的船只
First in the form of AI-controlled enemy vessels
首先以AI控制的形式 加入到敌方的船只中
and later, if we are happy with the results of the closed beta,
在此之后 如果我们对内测的结果感到满意
as an integral part of the naval research tree.
（大型战舰将会）加入到完整的海军科技树中
Speaking about research, with ships, everything will be the same.
谈到研发 关于船只的一切都是相同的
You get research points during matches
你在游戏中获得的研究点
and later can spend them to get new ships and unlock new modules.
之后也可以把他们花在研发新船和解锁新改装件上面
Well, you know how it works.
当然 你知道这是怎么运作的
Needless to say, we're making some new spectacular maps for naval warfare.
不用说 我们正在为海战做一些新的壮丽地图
You are going to fight in every naval theatre of war,
你将在每个海战区域中战斗
in the Pacific, in the Atlantic, in the Arctic.
在太平洋 大西洋 北冰洋
and also in the Mediterranean sea.
甚至地中海
We are proud to say that the water surfaces in all new locations are created using NVIDIA Waveworks
我们可以自豪地宣布 所有新地图的水面使用NVIDIA Waveworks创建
so get ready for some breathtaking views.
为惊艳的景色做好准备吧
The full list of the first ships to enter the fray is going to be revealed at Gamescom.
在科隆游戏展 第一批可玩的船只将会展示出来
The visitors of Gamescom 2016 will also be the first to try the new mode.
2016年科隆游戏展的参观者将会在第一时间尝试这种新模式
For those unable to visit the exhibition (and, frankly, that will be the majority of us)
对于那些未能参观展会的人（实话说 我们大多数人都是这样）
there will be a special video broadcast from our booth
你将能看到来自我们摊位的一个特殊视频直播
and new devblog updates each day.
和每天的开发者博客更新
Stay tuned.
敬请关注
The last bit of information: we are also working on mixed battles involving ships.
最后一点 我们仍在混合战斗模式上努力
The mode where ships and aircraft are fighting together is being tested right now.
一种船舶和飞机一起战斗的模式正在被测试
TM
Well, to make the wait a little bit easier,
好吧 让Soon  时间不再那么TM
we are going to tell you a few wartime stories
我们会讲一些战时故事
that couldn't happen without the fast and deadly "Knights of the Sea".
如果没有这些快速致命的“海洋骑士” 这些故事就不可能发生
Pearl Harbor changed everything.
珍珠港事件改变了一切
The United States had to enter a full scale war.
美国不得不进入一个全面战争
For the US armed forces, the timing wasn't ideal
对于美军而言 时机并不理想
and doubly so for the Allied forces that were defending Philippines.
对于保卫菲律宾的盟军而言 这更加糟糕
All the big ships had left for the safety of the Dutch East Indies
为了保障荷属东印度群岛的安全性 所有的大船离开了
the fleet consisted of a few submarines
舰队里有一些潜艇
and the Motor Torpedo Boat Squadron Three, a detachment of six torpedo boats.
和三号鱼雷快艇中队 六艘鱼雷艇中的一艘
The Americans called them patrol torpedo boats – or PT boats.
美国人叫他们巡逻鱼雷艇 或者简称PT艇
The ever sharp-witted sailors called these vessels "Plywood Wonder".
向来机智风趣的船员称这些船只为“胶合板传奇”
These comparatively fragile boats with their wooden hulls were certainly not for the faint of heart.
由木制船体组成的相对脆弱的船只当然不适合那些胆小鬼使用
Luckily, Lt John D. Bulkeley, who commanded Motor Torpedo Boat Squadron Three,
幸运的是 指挥着三号鱼雷快艇中队的中尉约翰D·巴尔克利
certainly did not lack in the courage department.
理所应当地充满着勇气
Later he will play quite a big role in the war and will retire a vice-admiral.
后来 他将在战争中发挥相当大的作用 退休前担任海军中将
At the start of the war, though,
尽管在战争的开始
he was in charge of the small "mosquito-fleet" in the seas around Philippines.
他只负责菲律宾周边海域的小型“蚊子舰队”
And his boats definitely didn't fool around.
但他的船也绝不是游手好闲
For example, one night Bulkeley's boys spotted an enemy ship,
譬如 有天晚上巴尔克利的手下发现了敌舰
a Japanese cruiser screened by four destroyers.
是一艘由四艘驱逐舰护卫的日本巡洋舰
Apparently no prey was too big for these guys.
显然对他们而言 就算是巨大的猎物也能拿下
Without much ado they fired their torpedoes.
他们毫不犹豫地发射了自己的鱼雷
In the end the Americans had to pay for their reckless bravery.
最后美国人不得不为他们不计后果的勇敢付出了代价
One of the boats went down.
一艘船被击沉
But they were able to damage the Japanese cruiser Kuma and that's what counts.
但是他们摧毁了球磨级轻巡洋舰 是坠吼的
No wonder the Japanese called these little vessels "devil boats".
怪不得日本人把这些赛艇成为“魔鬼船”
But Bulkeley's finest hour came in March, 1942.
不过到了1942年3月 巴尔克利迎来了他最辉煌的时刻
By that time the detachment diminished to just four PT's, including Bulkeley's PT-41.
到那时 即使把巴尔克利的PT-41也算在内 支队也减少到只有四艘PT艇
The future looked grim for the defenders of the islands.
对于岛屿的守卫者而言 未来是残酷的
It was decided that General Douglas MacArthur, who was commanding the Allied forces in the region,
中央已经研究决定了 盟军的长官道格拉斯·麦克阿瑟将军
had to leave Philippines and relocate to Australia.
必须离开菲律宾 同时转进到澳大利亚
It seems that MacArthur wasn't particularly fond of submarines.
麦克阿瑟好像并不喜欢坐潜艇
He decided to go by Bulkeley's boat, to be exact.
准确地来讲 他决定坐巴尔克利的赛艇去
Now you have to consider this.
现在你可以想象一下
Yeah, Bulkeley, whom the general once described as "That bold buckaroo with the cold green eyes",
没错 巴尔克利 作为一个被描述为“有着冷绿色眼睛的莽撞牛仔”
was probably his best choice for that daring mission.
也许是这场冒险行动的最佳选择
But the lieutenant's PT's, that were not known for particular sturdiness in the first place,
但是 对于中尉那并不十分坚固的PT艇而言
had to cross over 600 nautical miles (or 1,000 km) of open ocean,
它们需要穿越超过600海里/1,000公里的开阔海域
while also breaking through Japanese lines.
同时突破日军的封锁线
And they did it,
他们成功了
saving the lives of MacArthur, his family and his staff.
保护了麦克阿瑟和他家人及工作人员的安全
It's small wonder that on arriving to safety MacArthur told Bulkeley,
这也难怪当麦克阿瑟刚到安全位置的时候 就和巴尔克利说道
"You have taken me out of the jaws of death. I shall never forget it."
你把我从鬼门关中救出 我永远也不会忘记
And now let's leave the warm waters of the Far East to speak about a suicidal attack
现在 让我们离开远东的温暖水域来谈论一下自杀式袭击
on the most important dry dock of the Third Reich.
在第三帝国最重要的干船坞
The colossal German battleship Tirpitz was a serious problem.
在巨大的德国战舰提尔皮茨是一个严重的问题
This marvel of engineering could single-handedly act as a deterrent against an Allied invasion
这一工程奇迹能够凭借一己之力遏制住盟军的入侵
and that's saying something.
这意味着
Head-on attack on such a ship didn't sound very tempting.
正面进攻这艘船并不是一个好的选择
In the end the British decided to take a different approach.
最终英国决定采取不同的方法
There was only a handful of places around the world that could accommodate the German monstrosity
在那时的世界上只有很少一部分船坞能容纳德国的庞然大物
in case it needed repairs.
而这些船坞则被用作维修
And there was only one safe haven available on the Atlantic coast,
而在大西洋 只有一个安全的船坞可用
the French dock at St Nazaire.
就是法国的船坞圣纳泽尔
No dock – no repairs, so the dock had to be destroyed.
没有船坞意味着没法修理 所以船坞必须予以摧毁
The problem was that the Admiralty refused to spare even a single functional destroyer
问题是英国海军部甚至不想出动一艘在役的驱逐舰
as they were likely to be lost during the assault.
因为他们可能在进攻期间损失
That's why when the British got ready for the mission,
这就是为什么英国人为这次任务组织了这样的一支队伍
the attacking force consisted of a group of motor launches
这支队伍由摩托艇
and the obsolete HMS Campbeltown.
和过时的英国皇家海军坎贝尔城号驱逐舰组成
(that was originally US destroyer USS Buchanan)
（这本来是美国驱逐舰布坎南号）
There was a twist though, the ship was packed with delayed-action explosives.
虽然有些一波三折 这艘船装满了带有延迟引信的炸药
So yeah, a floating time bomb and a flotilla of 16 motor launches
没错 漂浮的延迟炸弹和由16艘摩托艇组成的小型船队
had to take down the heavily defended dock at St Nazaire.
要拆掉这个防守严密的圣纳泽尔码头
The British plan was simple.
英国人的计划很简单
Use HMS Campbeltown to ram the dock and then, blow it sky high.
使用皇家海军坎贝尔城号冲撞船坞 接着把它炸上天
The boats were supposed to land a small force of commandos
这些船需要由一小部分突击队员来驾驶
to destroy machinery and defend structures.
去摧毁造船机械和防守工事
The German plan was even simpler.
德国人的计划更是简单
Not to let the Royal Navy in and preferably not to get blown up.
别让皇家海军攻入 最好别让它炸毁这里
On the evening of the 26th of March the British convoy left Falmouth, Cornwall.
在3月26日晚间 英国护航队离开了康沃尔郡的法尔茅斯
On the 27th RAF organized a series of bombing runs against the German positions at St Nazaire,
在27日 英国皇家空军对圣纳泽尔的德军阵地进行了一系列的轰炸
which failed to produce any meaningful results and only made the defenders of the port extra watchful.
然而这并没有太大意义 还让防御船坞的德国人提高了警惕
Everyone was placed on a heightened state of alert
每个人都提高了警惕
and the commander of the German forces ordered extra attention
与此同时德军的指挥官要求需格外注意
to be paid to the approaches to the harbor.
那些通往港口的海域
Brilliant.
这真是坠吼的
At 01:22, with the convoy roughly 1 mile (1.6 km) from the dock gates,
01:22的时候 护航队抵达了距离船坞入口大约1英里（1.6公里）的位置
the British ships were illuminated by the German searchlights
英国人的船被德国人的探照灯打亮了
and soon all hell broke loose.
很快全乱套了
Every German gun in the bay opened fire but it was too little too late.
海湾内的所有德军武器都开火了 但这已经太迟了
While being hit by enemy shells, Campbeltown rushed across the harbor and rammed the dock gates,
尽管被敌人的炮弹击中 坎贝尔城号快速穿过港口 撞向船坞大门
driving the ship 33 feet (or 10 metres) inside.
甚至把里面的船只推动了33英尺（或10米）
A few moments later the commandos poured from Campbeltown looking for their targets.
过了一会儿 突击队从坎贝尔城号中涌出 寻找自己的目标
That was when the first motor boats started to arrive through the barrage.
当时正值第一批摩托艇穿过弹幕的时候
Boat No.156 got hit at least once while trying to disembark its assault team,
当156号船要登陆让突击队员上岸时 受到了至少一次攻击
but miraculously was able to get away to the open sea.
但奇迹般地得以脱身并再度返回到大海中
No.192 and 262 went down.
192号和262号船沉没了
Only five people from their crew surviving the ordeal.
这两艘船中只有五人在这样严峻的考验下生还
Most of the boats had been destroyed on the run in.
大多数船只在突击的途中就被击沉了
But a few of them managed to disembark their commandos
但也有一些船成功地让他们的突击队员登陆了
that quickly tried to locate their targets under heavy enemy fire.
在敌人的重火力之下 突击队迅速地瞄准了目标
The sea was aflame.
整个海面都燃烧了起来
Aboard ML 306 Sergeant Thomas Durrant was spraying the Germans with bullets with his twin Lewis gun.
ML 306船上的海军中士托马斯·达兰特使用他兄弟刘易斯的枪对德国人进行扫射
He refused to leave his post
他拒不撤退
even after he was wounded in the head, both arms, legs, chest and stomach
即使是头部 四肢 胸部和腹部受伤后 仍在坚持
and even after ML 306 was attacked at short range by the German torpedo boat Jaguar.
甚至在ML 306被德国黑豹鱼雷艇近距离攻击后
His gun stopped firing only when ML 306 was finally boarded by Germans.
当ML 306终于被德国人登上时 他的枪才停止射击
Durrant was posthumously awarded a Victoria Cross.
达兰特身后被追授维多利亚十字勋章
The only such award given to a soldier in a naval action
这是在海军行动中 唯一被授予该荣誉的士兵
and on the recommendation of the enemy commander!
甚至闻名于敌方指挥官
It wasn't all in vain though.
这一切当然不是徒劳
In the morning, Campbeltown went up in flames
当天上午 坎贝尔城号付之一炬
and with it – a few dozens of German officers that were inspecting the vessel at that very moment.
同时被烧死的还有数十个恰好在检查船只的德国军官
Needless to say, the dock was destroyed.
不用说 船坞被摧毁了
In the end, only 228 men out of 662 got back to the friendly shores.
最后 662人中只有228回到了友军的港口
169 Brits were captured – after they ran out of ammo.
169个英国人在弹药耗尽后被俘虏
Five got through the town and escaped into the countryside.
5个穿过了城镇并逃入了农村
Much later, with some aid from the French resistance, they got home through Spain.
后来他们得到了法国抵抗军的援助并通过西班牙回到家
As it often happens, both sides counted it as a victory.
由于这类事情经常发生 双方都把它算作胜利
But what we know for sure is that no Tirpitz ever got the chance to get its repairs at the dock of St Nazaire!
但是 我们肯定知道的是 提尔皮茨并没有得到在圣纳泽尔码头维修的机会
Finally it's time for the traditional last part of our show: Hotline!
最后 按照传统 到了我们节目了的最后部分 热线
Developers answering questions from the comments!
开发者将回答评论中的问题
Strictly speaking it's not the most serious-minded section of the show.
严谨地说这不是该节目中最认真的部分
If you want answers to be given with solemn faces, feel free to appeal to the official forums.
如果你想获得更郑重的回答 请到官方论坛提问
Here we'll have a more light-hearted discussion of the big questions of War Thunder.
在这儿我们会对战争雷霆的一些重大问题进行更轻松的讨论
We hope you'll like it.
希望你会喜欢它
注：tk指在游戏中杀死队友的行为
Michael Mwai asks: "Will Gaijin implement a mechanism to punish team-killers in Custom Battles?"
Michael Mwai问道 在自定义战斗中 Gaijin会实施惩罚tk行为的机制吗
Hello, Michael! We actually have a special system that finds players like this and bans them.
你好 迈克尔 事实上 我们拥有一个能发现tk行为并封禁他们的特殊机制
It doesn't happen with the first kill though.
在第一次tk的时候这个机制并不会起作用
So you have to be a serious offender.
因此 想要触发机制 你肯定tk过很多次了
And in Custom Battles the host can also simply kick the players
而在自定义战役中 房主也可以轻松地踢掉
that are too busy fighting their own teammates. Power to the people!
那些忙于和队友作战的玩家 权力是属于人民的
A guy called Thunders CZ says: "Night battles are rare. And why are they rare?﻿"
Thunders CZ说 为什么夜间战斗很罕见
Well, basically because night fighting is not very popular.
好吧 基本上是因为夜战是不是很受欢迎
Same thing with extreme weather conditions.
极端的天气条件也是如此
We know that some people really enjoy the challenge though.
不过我们知道 有些人很喜欢迎接挑战
That's why you can easily make yourself a night map in Custom Battles.
因此你也可以在自定义战斗里的夜战地图中获得满足
I hope that helps.
希望你能获得帮助
Then a question from Notenoughdata: "Will submarines be part of Naval Combat?"
来自Notenoughdata的一个问题 潜艇将会是海军作战的一部分吗
This question has been asked a lot so here it is again, guys.
这个问题已经被问了很多 所以这里要再次重申 伙计们
We haven't even introduced naval battles to the game yet
我们还没有正式推出海战模式
and you are already asking questions about specific content, geez.
而你已经在提关于具体内容的问题了 天了噜
But we can say that we are not planning to have submarines in War Thunder...at least at the very start.
不过可以说的是 至少在海战刚开始的时候 我们不打算推出潜艇
TM
Subs are fascinating, but also... rather slow.
潜艇很迷人 但是也需要Soon  的时间
And we want to see some fast action that will get your blood boiling, so they do not really match our profile.
我们想搞点快速的作战能让你们热血沸腾 所以潜艇并不真正符合我们的要求
Finally a very important question from benjamin wehrle: "Why did update 1.61 come out so fast?"
最后 benjamin wehrle提了个非常重要的问题 为什么1.61更新来得这么快
Sorry about that, it's a real shame, we know.
对此感到抱歉 这确实有些遗憾 我们知道
We just wanted to introduce a very important mechanic called Reinforcement as fast as we could.
我们在推出这个特别重要的候补机制上花费了太多时间
Sorry again. We will be slower next time!
再次抱歉 我们下次更新会慢一些
That's it for today but feel free to write your questions in the comments below.
今天就这些了 但是也请各位在评论区畅所欲言
We do read them all, and you might see some of them answered in the next episode!
我们会把每个评论都阅读一遍 在下一集中你或许能看到一些问题得到了回答
See you on the Shooting Range!
下一集Shooting Range再见